

ashleylkunze.com ashley@ashleylkunze.com 913.660.3638

I design on purpose.

I use my perceptiveness and adaptability to make intentional decisions that solve problems. I believe in combining empathetic relating with organized strategy to facilitate restoration and create innovative designs. My intuition and discipline drive me to design experiences that work.

Professional Experience

WEB DESIGNER

Garmin International January 2016–present

Design and develop email campaigns, web pages and online marketing materials; setup new email campaign strategy and procedure in AEM and train international teams.

Supervisor: Christine Marko, 913.440.5086

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Kiewit Engineering & Design Co. May 2015–December 2015

Design department brand identity, digital marketing materials, proposal templates, event packaging and presentation graphics; transform complex technical information into effective infographics.

Supervisor: Leisha Harrison, 913.907.9127

WEBMASTER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

John Brown University Visual Arts Department August 2013–December 2015

Organize, design, write, and manage department website, email campaigns, print and digital marketing materials, and social media content.

Supervisor: Jeannie Abbott, 479.238.8561

Education

John Brown University, Siloam Springs, AR Bachelor of Science: Graphic & Web Design Graduated in December of 2015

Professional Skills

Graphic Design & Interactive Design

UI/UX Design, Marketing, Copywriting, Creative Research, Photo Retouching, Hand Lettering, Typography, Social Media, Branding, Pencil/Ink Drawing

Personal Skills

Organization, Empathy, Planning, Efficiency, Question-Asking, Problem-Solving, Story-Telling, Decision-Making

Technical Skills

Adobe Experience Manager, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Experience Design, Sketch

HTML, CSS, Wordpress

Social Media

f /AshleyLKunze

in /AshleyLKunze

p /AshleyLKunze

/AshleyLKunze

